Stephanie Aurelio

Hello.

LOS ANGELES, CA PHONE 916-420-0772

E-MAIL

stephanie.m.aurelio@gmail.com

PROFILE

Ex-librarian turned developer with a background in libraries and museums. Adept at learning new tech, research, information organization/visualization, and collaborative work environments. Experienced with databases and information management systems. Currently pursuing education in full-stack development through UCLA Extension.

EXPERIENCE

LIBRARIAN, CITY OF SANTA MONICA; SANTA MONICA, CA NOV 2018 - AUG 2019

Developed, marketed, and implemented programs in accordance with outcomes-based metrics and survey data. Reference services, tech instruction, and system-wide event planning. Managed teen volunteer program.

LIBRARIAN, CITY OF MONROVIA; MONROVIA, CA SEP 2017 - OCT 2018

Grant writing and management for public programming. Collection development, materials cataloging, and classification. Volunteer management.

LIBRARIAN, SACRAMENTO PUBLIC LIBRARY, SACRAMENTO, CA MAY 2015 - JULY 2017

Community collaborator with a focus on building partnerships to provide innovative, health-based programming for a library in a Building Healthy Communities promise zone. Outreach to schools, parent groups, and community centers.

MEMBERSHIP ASSISTANT, CROCKER ART MUSEUM; SACRAMENTO, CA NOV 2013 - JAN 2015

Database management for member/donation database charged with adding, editing, and merging records, running reports, and exporting data. Wrote database best practices for training new hires. Collaborated with departments on member events.

EDUCATION

SAN JOSE STATE UNIVERSITY; SAN JOSE, CA MASTER'S, LIBRARY AND INFORMATION SCIENCE - 2015 CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, SACRAMENTO; SACRAMENTO, CA BACHELOR OF ARTS, HISTORY - 2010

SKILLS

- · Windows & Mac OS, Microsoft Office Suite, Google suite
- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Git

CONNECT

LINKEDIN GITHUB

linkedin.com/in/stephaniemaurelio/ github.com/stephmarie17/portfolio